Hi Hi everyone how are you wherever you
are back again my page You are
fine and you are always
protected by God Almighty
Hi well good afternoon
Hi Today I want to educate
about health
hi why should it be health
Hi I give philosophy Suppose
Hi guys I have no more savings there are
none and I was hit by an
accident
illness or what is angry
now is the conflict of
the Coffin emping teams very angry
very angry and
Hi that is a
technique to require you to have
health insurance which is certain
Hi well
The belgica Copy initially if I
don't have money what do I do
green brother borrow family or
borrow from the Foundation ask for help from the
Foundation
try to feel it is impossible
therefore let's set aside your money for
1 Stabat opinion per day only
Rp. 35,000 and you have seen that it has
very super facilities serviced
in this Power section ask United odm
after directly face Okay just ask
well
Hi thank you for watching
my video like if you like
comment if you don't agree and series
your friends if you think
my video is good thank you
friends have  watch bye bye